[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the cause of one of the deadliest airplane disasters in history that happened on 26 April 1994 with China Airlines Flight 140?", "correct_answer": "Pilot error", "incorrect_answers": ["Overload", "Fire", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Laura is one of the most memorable films made in the Film Noir genre, even more so thanks to Clifton Webbs performance.  What was his film characters name?", "correct_answer": "Waldo Lydecker", "incorrect_answers": ["Whit Sterling", "Jules Amthor", "Kaspar Gutman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the lemur Aye-aye?", "correct_answer": "It is the largest nocturnal primate on the planet.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is the second smallest primate on the planet.", "It is the second largest primate in the world.", "It is the smallest nocturnal primate in the world."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This term denotes the process of adding sugar to the must, the juice of the freshly pressed grapes, in order to increase alcohol content in wine.", "correct_answer": "chaptalization", "incorrect_answers": ["crackling", "maceration", "fining"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of animal character, named Master Shifu, did Dustin Hoffman voice in the 2008 animated movie Kung Fu Panda?", "correct_answer": "Red Panda", "incorrect_answers": ["Tiger", "Snow Leopard", "Javan Rhinoceros"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What phobia is defined as fear of darkness?", "correct_answer": "Achluophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Acousticophobia", "Agliophobia", "Agraphobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 2001 movie is this audio clip from?", "correct_answer": "A Knights Tale", "incorrect_answers": ["First Knight", "Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves", "Black Knight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the B vitamins is known as thiamine?", "correct_answer": "Vitamin B1", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin B3", "Vitamin B2", "Vitamin B12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the suffix lith refer to (as in Neolithic Age)?", "correct_answer": "Stone", "incorrect_answers": ["Iron", "Copper", "Early tools"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What group included Nils Lofgren, Ray Bittan, Gary Tallent, and Soozie Tyrell?", "correct_answer": "The E Street Band", "incorrect_answers": ["The Eagles", "The Dave Mathews Band", "Aerosmith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Bruces humble comment when the kids admire his jaw-dropping Saleen S7 in the movie Bruce Almighty?", "correct_answer": "It gets me from A to B.", "incorrect_answers": ["No, you gotta see my new one.", "Just an old ramshackle.", "This is a necessity, not luxury."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these fish is a major source of omega-3 fatty acids?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Tuna", "Salmon", "Mackerel"]}]